let quiz = [
    {
        question: "In which country is this World Cup taking place?",
        option: [
            "In Qatar",
            "In Ukraine",
            "In Russia",
            "In China",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the 2018 World Cup mascot?",
        option: [
            "Zerbaky",
            "Zibyka",
            "Zabivaka",
            "Zabivaky",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who will Portugal play their first game against?",
        option: [
            "Morocco",
            "Spain",
            "Iran",
            "Austria",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which country is not in the group of France?",
        option: [
            "Australia",
            "Denmark",
            "Peru",
            "Switzerland",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Check the ball of this cup.",
        option: [
            "Roteiro",
            "Tango 12",
            "Telstar 18",
            "...",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "How much is France in the FIFA ranking? (10/06/2018)",
        option: ["6th", "7th", "8th", "9th"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What great team is not qualified for this World Cup?",
        option: [
            "Spain",
            "Belgium",
            "UItaly",
            "Brazil",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Mohamed Salah will not be present because of injuries. True or false?",
        option: ["True", "False", "...", "..."],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who will coach the Brazilian team for this Cup?",
        option: ["Peeled", "Dunga", "Tite", "..."],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What band is Argentina in?",
        option: ["Group B", "Group C", "Group D", "Group E"],
        answer: 3,
    },
];